Guide to the Gay Cable Network Archives, 1982-2001 MSS.231
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series XXXI: Objects, 253085
  - Wooden camera with "GCN" on front, Undated; cuid6906; 253045 (Box 180, Object ID: 231.2.0002)